

CAREER OBJECTIVES

To secure opportunity in a goal oriented and training stimulated environment, where I can add value, boost my skills, expertise and experience in contribution to the growth and development of the organization, and also to apply the creative power of my mind in the pursuit of the organizational goals and desires within the spere of my strength, passion and intelligence.

### SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

- Over two years of experience in customer service and administrative support positions
  Excellent knowledge Microsoft Office applications, Social media and good knowledge of Digital Marketing
  Strong team player who can work well individually or within a clturally diverse team
- · Fluent in written and spoken English

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Head Office Support Representative (2018 - present)

C&I Leasing Plc, Lekki, Lagos, NIG (outsourced to Access Bank Plc)

- Provide data management services to customers and bank's branches
- Provide excellent customer services to bank's btanches
- · Carry-out all transactions as specified and required by my supervisor and/or unit head

#### Personal Assistant and Social Media Manager (2016 - 2018)

Wondrous Hair Salon, Victoria Island, Lagos, NIG

- · Manage Boss's time, calendar and schedule
- Arrange, organize and manage all meetings and events
- Book flights, hotels, appointments
- · Organize and manage all campaigns, marketing strategies both online and offline
- · Design social media graphics; manage all social media accounts and company's website
- Perform administrative duties according to established procedures
- Fill in at front desk when there is shortage of staff

### Customer Service Assistant(2015 - 2016)

Sunej Global Ventures, Lagos, NIG

- · Provided excellent customer service to existing and prospective clients
- · Oversaw all sales of products and services
- · Handled and resolved all customers' complaints and queries
- · Properly managed daily financial reports and sales books
- · Performed all related administrative duties according to procedures

### Social Media PR(2011 - 2012)

Buzzwarehauz, Surulere, Lagos, NIG

- · Promoted Clients' businesses' online
- · Improved Client's social media presence
- Handled social media campaigns by providing written campaign strategies
- Attended meetings with both old and prospective clients
- Brand management

## PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

## Certification in Customer Service Skill(2017)

E-Learning Center (Employme Nigeria), Lagos, NIG

# EDUCATION

### Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science(In View)

National Open University of Nigeria, Lagos, NIG

### National Diploma, Quantity Surveying (2015)

Delta State Polytechnic, Ozoro, Delta, NIG

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Computer Skills: Ms Office Suite, Email and Internet Applications, Social Media applications, Quickbooks POS

Languages: English

### REFERENCES

Avaialable Upon Request